documents = [
    {
        'id': 1,
        'question': 'They call me and ask for Kaspi Gold card details. How to make sure they are not scammers ?',
        'answer': 'Kaspi.kz employees never ask for personal information about customers.Do not tell anyone, and do not indicate your data in correspondence and on websites. Anyone who asks you to do this is a scammer, even if they claim to be a Kaspi.kz employee.'
    },
    {
        'id': 2,
        'question': 'I want to see my credit history. Where can I get a credit report ?',
        'answer': 'You can get a credit report: on the egov website, in the public service centers of your city, in the office of the First Credit Bureau in Almaty.A credit report is provided free of charge once a year.'
    },
    {
        'id': 3,
        'question': 'The Kaspi Gold card has expired. Can I use it in the Kaspi.kz mobile application ?',
        'answer': 'Yes. You can for example receive salary benefits and other transfers by account number,fill in Kaspi Gold at Kaspi ATMs and Kaspi Terminals using IIN and QR code,make purchases using a QR code from Kaspi.kz partners'
    },
    {
        'id': 4,
        'question': 'How to open Kaspi Red ?',
        'answer': 'You can open Kaspi Red at any time online in the Kaspi.kz mobile application.Log in using the phone number that you specified when registering in the Kaspi.kz mobile application.Select "Open Kaspi Red" on the main page or in the "My Bank" service and follow the next steps. You will see the decision on the application in a minute on the screen of your smartphone.To complete the registration, confirm your identity: go through photo verification and sign the application with an electronic digital signature Kaspi.kz.'
    },
    {
        'id': 5,
        'question': 'The Kaspi Gold card has expired. What to do ?',
        'answer': 'You can reissue a Kaspi Gold card at any Kaspi Kartomat. This will take 60 seconds. Re-issuance at the end of the card validity period is free.'
    },
    {
        'id': 6,
        'question': 'What is the interest rate on Kaspi Deposit ?',
        'answer': 'Deposits in Kaspi.kz have the following annual interest rates: Effective rateremuneration: Tenge = 15%, US dollars = 1%'
    },
    {
        'id': 7,
        'question': 'I bought a product in the Store on Kaspi.kz. Will I receive Kaspi Bonuses ?',
        'answer': 'Yes. For purchases in the Store on Kaspi.kz with Kaspi Gold, you get 0.25 percent bonuses.Bonuses are awarded after receiving the goods.When buying goods in the Store on Kaspi.kz in installments, on credit or for Kaspi bonuses, Bonuses are not awarded.'
    },
    {
        'id': 8,
        'question': 'What is Kaspi Bonus? and How to get Kaspi Bonus ?',
        'answer': 'Kaspi Bonus is thanks to our beloved customers who buy and pay with Kaspi.kz.Participation in the program allows you to accumulate 0.25 percent bonuses for each purchase with Kaspi Gold when paying by Kaspi QR'
    },
    {
        'id': 9,
        'question': 'How to register in the Kaspi.kz mobile application ?',
        'answer': 'Download and install the Kaspi.kz mobile application.To register, you need to provide a mobile phone number, go through photo verification and follow the instructions on the screen.You can register in the Kaspi.kz mobile application only with the number of a Kazakhstani telecom operator.'
    },
    {
        'id': 10,
        'question': 'What are the restrictions on transfers in the Kaspi.kz mobile application ?',
        'answer': 'limit when transferring money to Kaspi Client 2 million tenge, between own accounts 10 million tenge, international transfers 10000 dollars'
    },
    {
        'id': 11,
        'question': 'What documents can be obtained in the Kaspi.kz mobile application ?',
        'answer': 'In the Kaspi.kz application you can get documents: on protection for all loans in Kaspi and Kaspi Red;about the presence of a Kaspi Gold or Kaspi Deposit account;about the available amount with a Kaspi Gold or Kaspi Depositu statement (suitable for tax and embassies).'
    },
    {
        'id': 12,
        'question': 'Where can I find out the details of my Kaspi Gold card ?',
        'answer': 'You can find out the details of Kaspi Gold in the Kaspi.kz mobile application.To do this, open the service "My Bank" → Kaspi Gold → Info → Card or account details, and then select the desired tab: "Card" or "Account".Here you can view card details for transfers or online purchases, as well as account details. Details can be copied or sent using the messenger or email installed on your smartphone.'
    },
    {
        'id': 13,
        'question': 'In which stores can I buy in installments with Kaspi Red ?',
        'answer': 'With Kaspi Red, you can shop at the Kaspi Store and from Kaspi.kz partners.'
    },
    {
        'id': 14,
        'question': 'How to change the limit for online payments with Kaspi Gold  ?',
        'answer': 'You can change the Kaspi Gold card payment limit for online purchases on Kaspi.kz: My Bank → Kaspi Gold → Actions → Online payment.The new limit can be used immediately after the change.'
    },
    {
        'id': 15,
        'question': 'I sent money to Kaspi Gold to the wrong person. What to do ?',
        'answer': 'You can send a request to cancel any transfer for the last month in the Kaspi.kz mobile application.Open the "Transfers" service, in the "History" section, select the desired receipt and click "Request Cancellation".According to the Law of the Republic of Kazakhstan “On Payments and Payment Systems”, a transfer can be returned only with the consent of the recipient. He will receive a message asking him to return the money. The recipient can do this within 7 days.If during this time you have not returned the money, you can apply to the court with a statement of claim.'
    },
    {
        'id': 16,
        'question': 'How to make a second transfer to Kaspi.kz ?',
        'answer': 'Go to the "Transfers" service in the application for mobile devices.In the "My transfers" section, all accounts with dropped out transfer amounts, and cards for which you have checked the "Save to Frequent" checkbox.Select the desired translation and click "Translate".'
    },
    {
        'id': 17,
        'question': 'What is Kaspi Red ?',
        'answer': 'Kaspi Red is a unique club for those who love installment purchases. Club members can buy in installments for 3 months in the best stores of clothing, childrens goods, perfumes, sporting goods and many others. No interest, no commissions and no overpayment.'
    }
]